<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	
xmlns:georss="http://www.georss.org/georss" xmlns:geo="http://www.w3.org/2003/01/geo/wgs84_pos#"
>

<channel>
	<title>cardnosh &#8211; Cardnosh</title>
	<atom:link href="https://cardnosh.com/blog/author/cardnosh/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog</link>
	<description>Blog</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 05:36:04 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.2.9</generator>

<image>
	<url>https://cardnosh.com/blog/wp-content/uploads/2019/01/favicon.png</url>
	<title>cardnosh &#8211; Cardnosh</title>
	<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
<site xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">165185185</site>	<item>
		<title>Sell your Gift Cards for Cash – Swap, Trade and Sell</title>
		<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog/sell-your-gift-cards-for-cash-swap-trade-and-sell/</link>
				<comments>https://cardnosh.com/blog/sell-your-gift-cards-for-cash-swap-trade-and-sell/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 05:35:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cardnosh]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cardnosh.com/blog/?p=45</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">If you own a lot of gift cards and now you are unsure about what to do with them, we suggest you to sell your gift cards for cash. It is prudent to understand that if your card has an expiry date, it may make selling it slightly challenging. These days, it has become trendy to offer gift cards to friends and relatives to mark a special occasion or during festivals.</p><a class="more-link" href="https://cardnosh.com/blog/sell-your-gift-cards-for-cash-swap-trade-and-sell/">Continue Reading ...</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">If you own a lot of gift cards and now you are unsure about what to do with them, we suggest you to sell your gift cards for cash. It is prudent to understand that if your card has an expiry date, it may make selling it slightly challenging. These days, it has become trendy to offer gift cards to friends and relatives to mark a special occasion or during festivals. It is hugely appreciated as it gives you an opportunity to pick out services or products that holds value for you.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>What to do with cards you are not going to use?</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">If you have received gift cards from a retailer you won’t be using or don’t especially care for, you can sell your gift cards for cash instead of letting it go unused. The amount you will get in return will largely depend on the popularity of the gift card’s affiliated retailer.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">If you are looking forward to getting the most value out of the gift cards that are of no use for you, following certain tips can make things easier for you-</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Read Reviews About the Websites</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">There are several websites that allow people to exchange or sell their gift cards. Before approaching any website, it is prudent to do your homework and ensure steering clear from shady websites. Many of the sites will make tall claims and will sell your card but conveniently fail to pay you. Sometimes, the buyer drains the card and claim for a chargeback. Thus, deal only with the websites that you find reliable.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Sell the Gift Cards to Your Friends or Family Members</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">You can also consider selling unused gift cards to friends or relatives which can equally maximize value. While doing so, just keep a few caveats in mind. Many gift cards are unusable in all parts of the world.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Keep Card Expiry Date in Mind</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Many gift cards come with an expiry date. So, when you are planning to <a href="https://cardnosh.com/">sell gift cards for cash</a>, ensure that it is still valid for sometimes. Else, it will become quite challenging for you to sell the card.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://cardnosh.com/blog/sell-your-gift-cards-for-cash-swap-trade-and-sell/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">45</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Learn About Sell iTunes Gift Card and How to Sell Them for Cash</title>
		<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog/learn-about-sell-itunes-gift-card-and-how-to-sell-them-for-cash/</link>
				<comments>https://cardnosh.com/blog/learn-about-sell-itunes-gift-card-and-how-to-sell-them-for-cash/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Wed, 04 Sep 2019 05:35:28 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cardnosh]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cardnosh.com/blog/?p=47</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">If you own an iTunes Gift Card and have no plans to use it anytime soon, you can sell iTunes gift card for cash. It is easier to say than done as there are a lot of issues that you need to keep in mind to ensure you are not duped. Selling the gift card is undoubtedly a great idea but at the same time,</p><a class="more-link" href="https://cardnosh.com/blog/learn-about-sell-itunes-gift-card-and-how-to-sell-them-for-cash/">Continue Reading ...</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">If you own an iTunes Gift Card and have no plans to use it anytime soon, you can sell iTunes gift card for cash. It is easier to say than done as there are a lot of issues that you need to keep in mind to ensure you are not duped. Selling the gift card is undoubtedly a great idea but at the same time, you need to understand that the rates that are going to be offered to you are going to be very disappointing. Sometimes, you may get as low as 50 percent of its actual value. If you wish to make more money out of this deal, you need to know how to do it.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Understanding the fact that not all gift card websites are the same</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Before you take a step to sell iTunes gift card for cash, you need to understand that the websites offering you a platform for this purpose are different. Some websites may buy your gift card directly, but such websites are very limited. They may also charge a high commission fee for this purpose. There are websites where users immediately buy or sell cards offering faster and better exchange rates. This ensure quick payouts via mobile wallet services or bank wires. Again, such websites are few and may not offer encouraging rates. Lastly, there are international marketplaces which gives a lot of trader choices which results in better rates, and an opportunity to buy or <a href="https://cardnosh.com/itunes-gift-cards.html">sell iTunes gift cards for cash</a> at any time.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Premium Rates Offered by International Buyers</strong></p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Another point that you need to keep in mind is that this gift card is pedestrian in several parts of the world where it is easy to purchase them at supermarket counters, gas stations, etc. The countries where iTunes is not so popular like China, buyers are ready to buy these cards at even a premium rate. This way, there is greater potential to earn more when selling the gift card.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Keeping these points in mind will help you make a strategy to sell these cards and which is sure to give you excellent results.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://cardnosh.com/blog/learn-about-sell-itunes-gift-card-and-how-to-sell-them-for-cash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">47</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tips for Walmart Gift Card Exchange for Cash</title>
		<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog/tips-for-walmart-gift-card-exchange-for-cash/</link>
				<comments>https://cardnosh.com/blog/tips-for-walmart-gift-card-exchange-for-cash/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2019 10:53:32 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cardnosh]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cardnosh.com/blog/?p=41</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Walmart is one of the most popular stores that has been known for its amazing range of products. The store already enjoys an amazing clientele but launches a promotion from time to time with its Walmart Gift Cards. This time, Walmart has launched a scheme where they are trying to target the unwanted gift cards owners.</p><a class="more-link" href="https://cardnosh.com/blog/tips-for-walmart-gift-card-exchange-for-cash/">Continue Reading ...</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Walmart is one of the most popular stores that has been known for its amazing range of products. The store already enjoys an amazing clientele but launches a promotion from time to time with its Walmart Gift Cards. This time, Walmart has launched a scheme where they are trying to target the unwanted gift cards owners. They are given an opportunity to exchange their gift cards for cash.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">If you are a loyal Walmart customer and have a lot of gift cards that you wish to exchange for cash, you need to look for a reliable and reputed platform that offers the best and safest <a href="https://cardnosh.com/walmart-gift-card.html">Walmart Gift Card exchange for cash</a>. There is no point being a proud owner of gift cards that you are never going to use. Instead, it is better to exchange them for some quick cash. One just needs to stay clear from certain online platforms that have come into the limelight for duping and scamming gift card sellers.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">There are online platforms that are safe and buy gift cards directly from sellers. These cards are again sold to the buyers interested in them. User to user interaction is very low and many times, sellers end up getting as much as 92 percent of their card value. Here are a few tips that you should keep in mind when selling your gift card.</p>
<ol style="text-align: justify;">
<li>Understand that not all card’s value is the same. The price of purchase is largely dependent on the popularity of the merchant.</li>
<li>Prices of the cards vary from site to site. Another tip that will help you choose the best deal is knowing the fact that the same card can fetch different rates at different websites. Thus, choose a trusted website that is offering you the best value for your Walmart Gift Card.</li>
<li>If the card has your name on it, meaning, if you have a personalized gift card, it may not be possible for you to sell it. It is going to stick with you unless you plan to use it.</li>
</ol>
<p style="text-align: justify;">With the holiday season in full swing and many stores giving gift cards to their consumers, the buy and sell of the cards has increased to a significant extent.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://cardnosh.com/blog/tips-for-walmart-gift-card-exchange-for-cash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">41</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>How to Sell iTunes Gift Card With Ease?</title>
		<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog/how-to-sell-itunes-gift-card-with-ease/</link>
				<comments>https://cardnosh.com/blog/how-to-sell-itunes-gift-card-with-ease/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2019 10:50:17 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cardnosh]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cardnosh.com/blog/?p=39</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">People believe that gift cards are something that can never go wrong and it is going to be the best present for the recipient. But it is better to be honest. Many times, these gift cards are nothing but a pain. It just seems to miss the mark. Most of the people may not east at that specific restaurant or shop at that store.</p><a class="more-link" href="https://cardnosh.com/blog/how-to-sell-itunes-gift-card-with-ease/">Continue Reading ...</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">People believe that gift cards are something that can never go wrong and it is going to be the best present for the recipient. But it is better to be honest. Many times, these gift cards are nothing but a pain. It just seems to miss the mark. Most of the people may not east at that specific restaurant or shop at that store. Instead of holding on to such cards, it is better to just sell iTunes gift card for cash.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">It is not at all challenging to sell these cards, but one needs to be a little careful so that you don’t fall prey to the card resale scam. This problem can be avoided by selling cards only on trusted websites and do not get in touch with anyone on social media platform ready to buy the cards. Stay a bit cautious when dealing with the websites and you will be good. The safest and smartest way to sell these unwanted gift cards is using the legitimate exchange of gift cards. Start with a reputed platform that helps you to sell iTunes gift card with instant cash. A trusted gift card buyer will always keep your interests in mind and ensure that transacting with them is safe and pleasant experience. This way, they are able to ensure repeat business coming their way.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">It is significant to note that exchanges on an online platform is majorly dependent on supply and demand in the market. As a result, the websites pay more for cards that are in greater demand than for ones that are not so high on people’s wishlist. It is for this reason people are <a href="https://cardnosh.com/itunes-gift-cards.html">selling iTunes gift cards</a> which turned out to be the last year’s most resold gift card. People selling these cards got 65 percent of card value.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">When you sell the card on a reputed website, the payment is done within five minutes and sometimes before that. There are many payment options and sellers can choose any option as per their convenience. These options are Paypal, check another gift card, or electronic deposit. So, stay safe and enjoy a quick transaction.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://cardnosh.com/blog/how-to-sell-itunes-gift-card-with-ease/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">39</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tips on How to Sell iTunes Gift Card Online</title>
		<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog/tips-on-how-to-sell-itunes-gift-card-online/</link>
				<comments>https://cardnosh.com/blog/tips-on-how-to-sell-itunes-gift-card-online/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 12:02:04 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cardnosh]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cardnosh.com/blog/?p=33</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Perhaps you’ve heard about people who sell iTunes gift card online and wonder how you, too, can turn your unused or unwanted gift cards to cash. With the right buyer, your iTunes gift card or any other type of gift card can be redeemed to cash, easily. Various websites and companies offer this kind of service,</p><a class="more-link" href="https://cardnosh.com/blog/tips-on-how-to-sell-itunes-gift-card-online/">Continue Reading ...</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Perhaps you’ve heard about people who sell iTunes gift card online and wonder how you, too, can turn your unused or unwanted gift cards to cash. With the right buyer, your iTunes gift card or any other type of gift card can be redeemed to cash, easily. Various websites and companies offer this kind of service, but you should always be careful and vigilant in choosing a legitimate website to sell your gift cards to. Gift cards are widely resold everywhere and people who make the habit of reselling gift cards they receive typically fetch at least 65% of their total value. Payments are usually received through electronic deposit, payment platforms, and any other type of account that suits the seller’s convenience.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">When trying to sell iTunes gift card or any other type of gift card online, the most important thing you should remember is to look for a legitimate site to sell to. Gift cards are very attractive targets for online crooks, which is why it is important to be extra careful when trying to sell them online. While a gift card is something of a “can’t go wrong” present, it can also miss the mark at times, leaving you with a bunch of credit you wouldn’t want to go to waste. While re-gifting them is an option, a better way to make use of unwanted gift cards is to redeem them for cash.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The best gift card selling advice you can get is to watch out for fraudulent sites and scams that are only out for your cash and strip you of your card’s value without paying you back. Choose legitimate sites to <a href="https://cardnosh.com/itunes-gift-cards.html">sell iTunes gift card</a> and make sure that your money is safe with every transaction by using only reputable sites and companies that exchange gift cards for cash.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://cardnosh.com/blog/tips-on-how-to-sell-itunes-gift-card-online/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">33</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Exchange iTunes Gift Card for Money – Know Its Advantages</title>
		<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog/exchange-itunes-gift-card-for-money-know-its-advantages/</link>
				<comments>https://cardnosh.com/blog/exchange-itunes-gift-card-for-money-know-its-advantages/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Mon, 08 Jul 2019 12:02:30 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cardnosh]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cardnosh.com/blog/?p=35</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Gift cards are popular go-to presents, and while a lot of people do appreciate receiving them, especially when they are for a restaurant, store, or vendor that they frequent, there are also times when a gift card is of little to no use to the recipient. There is always the option to re-gift, but there lies the danger of the gift card being yet again unwanted,</p><a class="more-link" href="https://cardnosh.com/blog/exchange-itunes-gift-card-for-money-know-its-advantages/">Continue Reading ...</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Gift cards are popular go-to presents, and while a lot of people do appreciate receiving them, especially when they are for a restaurant, store, or vendor that they frequent, there are also times when a gift card is of little to no use to the recipient. There is always the option to re-gift, but there lies the danger of the gift card being yet again unwanted, unused, and left to go to waste. One of the best ways you can get value from an unwanted gift card is to sell them. When you exchange iTunes gift card for money, you save the gift from collecting dust in a drawer somewhere and going to waste before they expire.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">With gift cards being a $127 billion market, and showing no signs of slowing down, despite an estimated of a billion-dollar value in cards going unused on a yearly basis, it is not surprising how many businesses have found a way to cash in on unused cards by offering to exchange iTunes gift card for money. Today, websites and businesses offering to buy or exchange gift cards are growing in number and popularity and so are people opting to cash in on their unwanted gift cards.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">There are many advantages to selling gift cards online, not the least of which is getting money for an unusable or perhaps unwanted gift and shopping around for the best rate possible so as to make the most out of your gift card. When you <a href="https://cardnosh.com/sell-gift-cards-for-cash.html">exchange iTunes gift card for money</a>, the site can then resell the card at a discount to other people who actually need or want credit for a particular vendor. This way, you get to help other customers buy credit at a much lower rate, all the while receiving good value for an unwanted gift—a sure win-win proposition for everyone involved.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://cardnosh.com/blog/exchange-itunes-gift-card-for-money-know-its-advantages/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">35</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top 7 Secure Ways to Sell Gift Cards Online for Instant Cash</title>
		<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog/top-7-secure-ways-to-sell-gift-cards-online-for-instant-cash/</link>
				<comments>https://cardnosh.com/blog/top-7-secure-ways-to-sell-gift-cards-online-for-instant-cash/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2019 07:35:02 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cardnosh]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cardnosh.com/blog/?p=27</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Have you ever received a gift card that is no use to you? What about those that you never used and have already expired? Instead of re-gifting or disposing them, you may want to sell gift cards online for instant cash. That way, you do not have to feel sorry for not being able to use them.</p><a class="more-link" href="https://cardnosh.com/blog/top-7-secure-ways-to-sell-gift-cards-online-for-instant-cash/">Continue Reading ...</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Have you ever received a gift card that is no use to you? What about those that you never used and have already expired? Instead of re-gifting or disposing them, you may want to sell gift cards online for instant cash. That way, you do not have to feel sorry for not being able to use them. Just be sure that you are selling them using a safe and secure platform that has a proven record of being true to their claims. Here are some suggestions for selling your gift cards online:</p>
<ol style="text-align: justify;">
<li><strong>Sell them through online marketplaces</strong> – Some online marketplaces allow you to sell gift cards, but you need to prove your credibility to sellers and be careful of buyers posing to purchase them, only to scam to you in the end.</li>
</ol>
<ol style="text-align: justify;" start="2">
<li><strong>Sell through social media</strong> – You can sell gift cards on social media by making a post about it and setting it in public, but you need to be careful with bogus buyers who claim that they are willing to purchase them, only to leave you hanging or unpaid.</li>
</ol>
<ol style="text-align: justify;" start="3">
<li><strong>Find a trustworthy service provider</strong> – To avoid being scammed, sell gift cards online for instant cash only to fully registered businesses and platforms. Be sure to cross-check their credentials, so you can be sure that they are legal. They should be highly recommended by top platforms, too.</li>
</ol>
<ol style="text-align: justify;" start="4">
<li><strong>Trade –</strong> Some companies will offer to trade your gift cards with others that might be of use to you. Just make sure that they are a legitimate business.</li>
</ol>
<ol style="text-align: justify;" start="5">
<li><strong>Verify the credibility of the buyers</strong> – Whether you intend to trade or sell gift cards online for instant cash, take the time to verify the authenticity of their buyers. It might be best to consider selling to a trusted company to save time and avoid the hassle.</li>
</ol>
<ol style="text-align: justify;" start="6">
<li><strong>Communicate with the buyer </strong>– Reputable platforms that let you <a href="https://cardnosh.com/">sell gift cards online for instant cash</a> allow you to make your own account in their website, or you can contact them through reliable messaging apps for more convenience.</li>
</ol>
<ol start="7">
<li style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Know the rates</strong> – Compare the current rates from each buyer and find the best one that will offer the most instant cash.</li>
</ol>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://cardnosh.com/blog/top-7-secure-ways-to-sell-gift-cards-online-for-instant-cash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">27</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Steam Gift Card Online – How They Work?</title>
		<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog/steam-gift-card-online-how-they-work/</link>
				<comments>https://cardnosh.com/blog/steam-gift-card-online-how-they-work/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2019 07:38:53 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cardnosh]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cardnosh.com/blog/?p=29</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">For avid gamers, a Steam gift card is always a great gift, especially for those who play on their desktop. But for some console gamers, it may not be a practical gift. If you received a Steam gift card and you find no use to it, consider selling it online instead of giving it away or letting it expire.</p><a class="more-link" href="https://cardnosh.com/blog/steam-gift-card-online-how-they-work/">Continue Reading ...</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">For avid gamers, a Steam gift card is always a great gift, especially for those who play on their desktop. But for some console gamers, it may not be a practical gift. If you received a Steam gift card and you find no use to it, consider selling it online instead of giving it away or letting it expire. That way, you could use the money to buy another gift card or gaming credits that will make sense to you. Exchanging a Steam gift card online is possible through legitimate gift card trading platforms that are registered with the Corporate Affairs Commission in Nigeria. They buy e-codes and physical cards, with or without receipts, in any denomination regardless of the country where the card is from, and they can pay you in minutes.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">When planning to exchange your Steam gift card online, be sure to find a trustworthy and highly recommended platform that is trusted by other gamers and businesses in Nigeria. That way, being scammed will be the least of your worries. Here’s how they work:</p>
<ul style="text-align: justify;">
<li><strong>Initiate the trade</strong> – Get in touch with the gift card trading platform online or through a secure messaging app. Leading platform typically trade on a messaging application like Whatsapp for interactivity, but they also allow customers to trade through their website.</li>
</ul>
<ul style="text-align: justify;">
<li><strong>Get rates</strong> – Tell them that you want to exchange a Steam gift card online and its amount. They will give you the current rate at which they will buy it. Reputable service providers always give the best rates.</li>
</ul>
<ul style="text-align: justify;">
<li><strong>Start trading</strong> – If you are good with the rate, you may now proceed with the trade. Upload a photo of a physical gift card or send the correct e-code. Wait for the verification, which should take only a minute or two.</li>
</ul>
<ul>
<li style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Give your bank details</strong> – After successful verification, you will be asked to send your bank name, account name, and account number to complete the exchange of the <a href="https://cardnosh.com/steam-gift-card.html">Steam gift card online</a>. You will get a screenshot notifying that the payment has been deposited to your account.</li>
</ul>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://cardnosh.com/blog/steam-gift-card-online-how-they-work/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">29</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>The Popularity of Exchanging iTunes Gift Card For Money</title>
		<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog/the-popularity-of-exchanging-itunes-gift-card-for-money/</link>
				<comments>https://cardnosh.com/blog/the-popularity-of-exchanging-itunes-gift-card-for-money/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Mon, 15 Apr 2019 07:14:27 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cardnosh]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cardnosh.com/blog/?p=20</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">The iTunes digital store of Apple may have the best of digital applications, including games. The value and popularity of the iTunes gift card is also immense. But in many instances, users may not require the gift card. These may be the cases when the user may be using a smartphone of some other operating system,</p><a class="more-link" href="https://cardnosh.com/blog/the-popularity-of-exchanging-itunes-gift-card-for-money/">Continue Reading ...</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">The iTunes digital store of Apple may have the best of digital applications, including games. The value and popularity of the iTunes gift card is also immense. But in many instances, users may not require the gift card. These may be the cases when the user may be using a smartphone of some other operating system, or when he or she may have his/her purchase preferences lying elsewhere. One may also need instant cash and not a gift card, through which he or she may buy some other gift that a person may really want. Because there are a number of reasons for exchanging an iTunes card for instant cash, there is immense popularity of this business segment. There are a number of websites where you can actually sell your iTunes card, in no more than 5 minutes, and get good value for it instantly, credited directly to your bank account. Here are some aspects that add to the popularity of the “exchange iTunes gift card for money” programs.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Certified and Registered Online Portals</strong></h3>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The best of online websites where you can sell your iTunes gift cards are registered with Nigeria Corporate Affairs Commission. These online web portals also get good rating and even recommendation from the leading and reputed print and digital media sources and publications. Some of these may include Techcobal, Techpoint Africa, Dailytrust Newspaper, and NaijaTech Guide among others.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Instant Selling</strong></h3>
<p style="text-align: justify;">You may not need more than 5 minutes to sell any of your iTunes gift cards online. You can <a href="https://cardnosh.com/itunes-gift-cards.html">exchange iTunes gift card for money</a> with the reputed firms through WhatsApp, or through the online website of the firm. Next, you will have to load the picture of the gift card, if it is a physical gift card. If you are having a digital iTunes gift card, you may be required to share the code of it with the representative of the firm. The representative will then verify the card in a minute or so. You will be asked for your bank details and the money will be credited directly to your bank. You also get a screenshot of the payment. Because the process is entirely hassle-free and takes so less time, it is immensely popular among people of all age groups who want to raise some instant money.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Comprehensive Services</strong></h3>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Apart from the iTunes gift card, you may also sell the Google Play gift cards or gift cards of other leading firms including Apple, Sephora, and others. These websites also present an opportunity for you to get instant cash, by selling cryptocurrencies including Bitcoin.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">As we can see consumers have today immense opportunities when they want to sell an iTunes gift card. The popularity of the segment is immense, but you should only trust the certified and authorised firms while selling your gift card.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://cardnosh.com/blog/the-popularity-of-exchanging-itunes-gift-card-for-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">20</post-id>	</item>
		<item>
		<title>Important Points to Mind While Exchanging Gift Cards for Cash</title>
		<link>https://cardnosh.com/blog/important-points-to-mind-while-exchanging-gift-cards-for-cash/</link>
				<comments>https://cardnosh.com/blog/important-points-to-mind-while-exchanging-gift-cards-for-cash/#respond</comments>
				<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2019 07:02:16 +0000</pubDate>
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[cardnosh]]></dc:creator>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>

		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://cardnosh.com/blog/?p=16</guid>
				<description><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">While the gift cards can be one of the more preferred presents and gifts nowadays, there are instances where you may not be able to use them. For instance, you may get a gift card of a store that does not have the inventory you like. In other cases, you may have a preference for particular online stores.</p><a class="more-link" href="https://cardnosh.com/blog/important-points-to-mind-while-exchanging-gift-cards-for-cash/">Continue Reading ...</a>]]></description>
								<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">While the gift cards can be one of the more preferred presents and gifts nowadays, there are instances where you may not be able to use them. For instance, you may get a gift card of a store that does not have the inventory you like. In other cases, you may have a preference for particular online stores. Because returning the gift cards may not be a viable option, the best way to utilise them before they get to be redundant is to exchange them for cash.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">There are trustable and reputed online website and businesses that can offer you the best value for your gift card. These firms may a deal in Gift cards of Amazon, Sephora, Google Play, Walmart, Apple, and of other leading firms. To get the best value and to make a reliable and hassle-free exchange, it is important that you consider certain important points when you want to exchange gift cards for cash.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>You will not get the full value for your card</strong></h3>
<p style="text-align: justify;">While you may easily get up to 92% of the gift card value in the form of cash, you may not get a hundred percent value of it. Because all companies dealing in gift card levy a small fee on the transaction, the value of your gift card gets marginally used when you exchange it. It is good to evaluate a card, analyse its usefulness, and sell it at the earliest possible time, when you are not going to use it. This will bring to the highest value for the card. Selling at reputed and trustworthy online portals may also provide you with a better deal.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Exchange your card at reputed websites</strong></h3>
<p style="text-align: justify;">If you wish to trade and <a href="https://cardnosh.com/itunes-gift-cards.html">exchange gift cards for cash</a>, you should see to it that the platform is registered under the Nigeria Corporate Affairs Commission. All authentic firms in this business are registered with the government agency. The firm will also provide to you the registration number, which reflects that it is truly recognised and certified to trade in the online/physical gift cards. The more reliable print and digital platforms in Nigeria including Techpoint Africa, Dailytrust Newspapers, and Information Nigeria among others will also recommend a trustworthy portal.</p>
<h3 style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Dealing in all kinds of cards</strong></h3>
<p style="text-align: justify;">See to it that your chosen company deals in all kinds of gift cards, including the Amazon, Google Play, Apple, Target, JC Penny, Steam, Sephora, and other cards. The leading platforms may also trade in other items like RMB and bitcoins. Such a platform is often more reliable, has better customer service, and has a large customer base as well. You can indulge in a long term partnership with them as well.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Choosing the right website will help you get the most value for your card, and will bring to you a hassle-free gift card exchange experience that may be over in less than 5 minutes. Do not compromise on the important aspects, to get the best deal for you.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">
]]></content:encoded>
							<wfw:commentRss>https://cardnosh.com/blog/important-points-to-mind-while-exchanging-gift-cards-for-cash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
		<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
						<post-id xmlns="com-wordpress:feed-additions:1">16</post-id>	</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
